<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drone Tech LTD</title>
    <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Drone Tech LTD</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://test.dtidrone.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research and Development Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/research/</guid>
      <description>Our research and development (R&amp;amp;D) services for drones focus on advancing UAV technology and creating innovative solutions that address the evolving needs of various industries&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing and Production Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/manufacuring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 15:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/manufacuring/</guid>
      <description>Our manufacturing and production services for drones encompass the entire lifecycle of UAV development, from design to final production. We specialize in creating high-quality,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing and Validation Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/testing/</guid>
      <description>We provide testing and validation services for drones to ensure optimal performance and reliability. These services include a comprehensive range of tests that cover &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maintenance and Support Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/maintenance/</guid>
      <description>Our maintenance and support services for drones are designed to ensure the long-term operability and reliability of UAVs. We offer comprehensive services,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulting and Advisory Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/consultant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/consultant/</guid>
      <description>We provide specialized consulting and advisory services to help clients navigate the rapidly evolving UAV (Unmanned Aerial Vehicle) and aerospace industries. Our expertise covers critical&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> ST-10V</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2022/09/24/st-10v/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2022/09/24/st-10v/</guid>
      <description>A VTOL Fixed-Wing Unmanned Aerial Vehicle (UAV) combines the best of both worlds from two drone types: vertical takeoff and landing (VTOL) and fixed-wing aircraft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Simulation Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/training/</guid>
      <description>Our training and simulation services for drones are designed to equip operators with the necessary skills and knowledge to effectively and safely utilize UAV technology. We offer comprehensive training programs that cover both theoretical and practical aspects of drone operation,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARGO LITE</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2021/08/01/cargo-lite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2021/08/01/cargo-lite/</guid>
      <description>CARGO LITE represents a significant advancement in drone technology, designed specifically to meet diverse operational needs across various industries. As a  &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Engineering Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/design/</guid>
      <description>We provide innovative design solutions tailored to meet specific aerospace and UAV requirements, ensuring optimal performance and compliance with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind Tunnel Instrumentation &amp; Equipment Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2015/10/02/instrument/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2015/10/02/instrument/</guid>
      <description>Our Wind Tunnel Instrumentation &amp;amp; Equipment Services provide  ..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target drone (Hadaf-1)</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2015/08/03/target/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/blog/2015/08/03/target/</guid>
      <description>The Hadf-1 Target Drone is a multi-functional, high-performance drone tailored for aerial target practice and a range of training exercises. Built for durability, it ..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://test.dtidrone.com/img/about.png&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;About&#34; width=&#34;60%&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Drone Tech Company is focused on meeting Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s growing national defense and commercial needs by offering cost-effective, high-performance UAVs and drone services. By leveraging local expertise and reducing dependence on foreign technology, the company aims to position itself as a leader in the UAV industry. In addition to UAV design and manufacturing, Drone Tech Company provides a range of drone services, including aerial mapping, surveillance, and remote sensing, to support both defense and commercial sectors. These services, combined with cutting-edge UAV technology, enable the company to contribute to the global aerospace supply chain while enhancing national capabilities. The company&amp;rsquo;s phased approach ensures that it can scale production efficiently while maintaining a focus on high-quality performance, competitive pricing, and local manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;GET IN TOUCH&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Drone Tech Company, we’re passionate about innovation and delivering top-tier UAV solutions. Whether you need advanced drones, expert engineering, or customized services, we’re here to exceed your expectations. Let’s take your capabilities to new heights! Reach out today—we’re excited to work with you!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us-&#34;&gt;Contact us :&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;+966-538131599&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dtidrone.com&#34;&gt;www.dtidrone.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@dtidrone.com&#34;&gt;info@dtidrone.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Services</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/drone_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/drone_services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://test.dtidrone.com/img/drone_ser/image1to2.png&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;Drone in Agriculture&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-survey--aerial-mapping&#34;&gt;1. Survey &amp;amp; aerial Mapping&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We offer precise survey and aerial mapping services using advanced UAV technology, enabling accurate topographic data collection, land use planning, and environmental monitoring with high-resolution imagery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s rapidly evolving world, the demand for accurate and comprehensive mapping and surveying has never been greater. Aerial mapping technologies, powered by drones and advanced imaging techniques, have revolutionized the way we gather and analyze data for urban planning, infrastructure development, environmental assessments, and agricultural management. By capturing high-resolution images and precise geographical information, these technologies facilitate informed decision-making, enhance project efficiency, and promote sustainable development. This document explores the key applications of aerial mapping in urban planning, infrastructure, area profiling, and agricultural services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind Tunnels</title>
      <link>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/wind-tunnels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://test.dtidrone.com/en/engineering_services/wind-tunnels/</guid>
      <description>The Advanced Low Speed Wind Tunnel is a state-of-the-art, closed-circuit wind tunnel featuring a rectangular test section.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
